tpub.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Statement - Integrated Publishing

Privacy & Security Notice  
---  
  
Thank you for visiting Integrated Publishing and reviewing our privacy policy. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website:  
  
 Information Collected and Stored Automatically  
  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

  1. The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website; 
  2. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site; 
  3. The date and time you access our site; 
  4. The pages you visit; and 
  5. If you linked to Integrated Publishing from another website, the address of that website.

We use this information to help us make the site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.  
  
---  
 If You Send Us Personal Information  
  
If you choose to provide us with personal information -- by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through the website -- we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. The information you provide will only be used for Integrated Publishing's marketing purposes and will not be sold to ANY external organizations..  
  
---  
 Site Security  
  
  1. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs commercial software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. 
  2. Except for authorized [law enforcement](http://armymilitarypolice.tpub.com/mp1001c/Law-Enforcement-55.htm) investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw [data logs](http://armyquartermaster.tpub.com/Qm4910a/Data-Log-28.htm) are used for no other purposes and are scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with National Archives and Records Administration guidelines. 
  3. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

---  
 Prohibitions  
  
Integrated Publishing will **not** link to any website that exhibits hate, bias, or discrimination. Furthermore, Integrated Publishing reserves the right to deny or remove any link that contains misleading information or unsubstantiated claims, or is determined to be in conflict with Integrated Publishing mission or policies.  
  
---
